<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS News – SERIES-D</title>
    <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com</link>
    <description>Funding news for SERIES-D</description>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parloa Raises $350M Series D at $3B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/parloa-raises-350m-series-d-at-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parloa, a New York- and Berlin-based provider of AI agents for enterprise customer experience, has secured $350 million in Series D funding at a $3 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by General Catalyst, with participation from existing investors EQT Ventures, Altimeter Capital, Durable Capital, and Mosaic Ventures. General …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Onebrief Closes $200M Series D at $2.15B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/onebrief-closes-200m-series-d-at-2-15b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Onebrief, a Honolulu, HI–based AI-powered platform designed to transform operational planning and decision‑making workflows for the military, has closed a $200 million Series D at a $2.15 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Battery Ventures and Sapphire Ventures, with participation from Salesforce Ventures, General Catalyst, and Insight Partners. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Torq Raises $140M Series D at $1.2B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/torq-raises-140m-series-d-at-1-2b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Torq, a New York–based AI security operations platform, has raised $140 million in a Series D funding round at a $1.2 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Merlin Ventures, with participation from existing investors including Evolution Equity Partners, Notable Capital, Bessemer Venture Partners, Insight Partners, and Greenfield Partners. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PolyAI Raises $86 Million Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/polyai-raises-86-million-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PolyAI, a New York–based company specializing in enterprise conversational AI solutions, has raised $86 million in a Series D funding round. Investors The round was co-led by Georgian, Hedosophia, and Khosla Ventures, with participation from NVentures, British Business Bank, Citi Ventures, Squarepoint Ventures, Sands Capital, Zendesk Ventures, and Point72 Ventures. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[fal Raises $140 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/fal-raises-140-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[fal, a San Francisco, CA-based platform for real-time generative media, has raised $140 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Sequoia, with major participation from Kleiner Perkins and new investments from Alkeon Capital and NVentures, alongside existing investors. Sequoia Capital is a venture capital firm headquartered …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eon Raises $300 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/eon-raises-300-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eon, a New York–based cloud backup platform, has raised $300 million in Series D funding, bringing its total capital raised to $500 million. Investors The round was led by Elad Gil of Gil Capital, with participation from returning investors Sequoia Capital, Lightspeed Venture Partners, Greenoaks, and BOND, tripling Eon’s valuation …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Federato Raises $100 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/federato-raises-100-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Federato, a San Francisco, CA–based AI-native insurance platform, has raised $100 million in Series D funding, bringing its total funding to over $180 million. Investors The round was led by Growth Equity at Goldman Sachs Alternatives, with participation from returning investors Emergence Capital, Caffeinated Capital, StepStone Group, and Pear VC. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cursor Secures $2.3B Series D at $29.3B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cursor-secures-2-3b-series-d-at-29-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cursor, a San Francisco, CA–based AI development platform, has raised $2.3 billion in Series D funding, bringing the company’s post-money valuation to $29.3 billion. Investors The round included continued support from Thrive, a16z, Accel, and DST, with new participation from Coatue, NVIDIA, and Google. Cursor Use of Funds The capital …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metropolis Secures $1.6B in Financing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/metropolis-secures-1-6b-in-financing</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metropolis, a Los Angeles, CA-based company that applies artificial intelligence to real-world environments, has secured $1.6 billion in financing. Investors The round includes a $1.1 billion Term Loan B arranged by JPMorgan Chase Bank, N.A., and a $500 million Series D equity funding led by a fund managed by LionTree. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Habit Factory Raises ₩35 Billion in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/habit-factory-secures-35-billion-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Habit Factory, a Seoul, South Korea-based AI-driven fintech company, has raised ₩35 billion in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Z Venture Capital (ZVC) and Smilegate Investment, with participation from Industrial Bank of Korea, IBK Venture Investment, Kolon Investment, KB Investment, and Shinhan Venture Investment. Z Venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AppZen Raises $180 Million in Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/appzen-raises-180-million-in-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AppZen, a San Jose, CA–based AI-native platform for autonomous finance, has raised $180 million in Series D growth funding. Investors The round was led by Riverwood Capital, a venture capital firm that invests in high-growth companies in the technology and technology-enabled industries. The firm focuses on established businesses with proven …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Framer Raises $100M in Series D at $2B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/framer-raises-100m-in-series-d-at-2b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Framer, an Amsterdam- and San Francisco-based professional website design platform, has raised $100 million in Series D funding at a $2 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by existing investors Meritech and Atomico. Meritech is a prominent late-stage venture capital firm based in Palo Alto, California. Founded in 1999, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capacity Raises Over $92.6 Million in Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/capacity-raises-over-92-6-million-in-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capacity, a St. Louis, Missouri-based AI-powered support automation platform for contact centers, has raised over $92.6 million in funding, bringing its total raised to more than $155 million. Investors The round includes $50 million in debt financing from Chicago Atlantic and a $42.6 million Series D equity round. The Series …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blue J Raises $122 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/blue-j-raises-122-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Blue J, a Toronto, Canada-based generative AI tax research platform, has raised $122 million in a Series D funding round. Investors The round was led by Oak HC/FT and Sapphire Ventures, with participation from Intrepid Growth Partners, Ten Coves Capital, and CPA.com. Oak HC/FT is a venture and growth equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbyne Raises $100 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/carbyne-raises-100-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbyne, a New York-based provider of cloud-native emergency communications and response solutions, has raised $100 million in Series D funding, bringing its total funding to $250 million to date. Investors The round included participation from AT&T Ventures, Axon Enterprise, Cox Enterprises, Global Medical Response, Hanaco Growth, Hercules Capital, RCM Private …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vanta Raises $150 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/vanta-raises-150-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vanta, a San Francisco, CA-based AI-powered trust management platform, has raised $150 million in a Series D funding round. Investors The round was led by Wellington Management, with participation from Goldman Sachs Alternatives, Sequoia, J.P. Morgan, Craft Ventures, Y Combinator, Atlassian Ventures, and CrowdStrike Ventures. Wellington Management is a privately …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ashby Raises $50 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ashby-raises-50-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ashby, a San Francisco, CA-based all-in-one recruiting platform, has raised $50 million in a Series D funding round. Investors The round was led by Mark McLaughlin at Alkeon Capital, with co-lead participation from Lachy Groom and support from F-Prime, Elad Gil, Gaingels, and other existing investors. Alkeon Capital is a …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boulevard Raises $80 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/boulevard-raises-80-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Boulevard, a Los Angeles, CA-based client experience platform for appointment-based self-care businesses, has raised $80 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by JMI Equity, with continued participation from Index Ventures and VMG Partners. Founded in 1992, JMI Equity is a growth equity firm focused on investing …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtru Raises $50M at a $500M Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/virtru-raises-50m-at-a-500m-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Virtru, a Washington, D.C.-based data-centric security company, has raised $50 million in a Series D funding round, doubling its valuation to $500 million. Investors The round was led by ICONIQ, with participation from Bessemer Venture Partners, Foundry, and The Chertoff Group. ICONIQ Capital is a San Francisco-based investment firm established …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MaintainX Raises $150 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/maintainx-raises-150-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MaintainX, a San Francisco, CA-based maintenance and asset management platform, has raised $150 million in Series D funding, bringing its total raised to $254 million, reaching a new valuation of $2.5 billion. Investors The round included key investors such as Bessemer Venture Partners, Bain Capital Ventures, D. E. Shaw Ventures, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clearspeed Raises $60 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/clearspeed-raises-60-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clearspeed, a San Diego, CA-based voice-based risk assessment technology company, has raised $60 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Align Private Capital, with additional participation from IronGate Capital Advisors, Bravo Victor Venture Capital, KBW Ventures, and multi-round investor General David H. Petraeus. Align Private Capital …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Snorkel AI Raises $100 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/snorkel-ai-raises-100-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Snorkel AI, a Redwood City, CA-based AI data development platform provider, has raised $100 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Addition, with participation from Prosperity 7 Ventures, Greylock, Lightspeed, BNY, and QBE Ventures. Addition is a venture capital firm focused on early- and growth-stage technology …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Buildots Raises $45 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/buildots-raises-45-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Buildots, a Tel Aviv, Israel-based construction technology company, has raised $45 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Qumra Capital, with participation from OG Venture Partners, TLV Partners, Poalim Equity, Future Energy Ventures, and Viola Growth. Buildots Use of Funds The company will use the funds …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact Analytics Secures Series D Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/impact-analytics-secures-series-d-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Impact Analytics, a New York-based provider of an end-to-end platform for pricing, merchandising, and supply chain management, has secured Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Blue Cloud Ventures, with participation from existing investors Sageview Capital and Vistara Growth. Blue Cloud Ventures is a growth-stage venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Veza Raises $108 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/veza-raises-108-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Veza, a Los Gatos, CA-based identity security company, has raised $108 million in Series D funding at an $808 million valuation. Investors The round was led by New Enterprise Associates (NEA), with strong participation from Atlassian Ventures, Workday Ventures, and Snowflake Ventures. All existing investors joined the round, including Accel, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Astronomer Raises $93 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/astronomer-raises-93-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astronomer, a New York-based company that provides a unified DataOps platform, has raised $93 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Bain Capital Ventures, with participation from Salesforce Ventures, Insight, Meritech, Venrock, and an expected investment from Bosch Ventures. Bain Capital Ventures is a venture capital …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chainguard Raises $356 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/chainguard-raises-356-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chainguard, a Kirkland, WA-based cybersecurity company, has raised $356 million in Series D funding at a $3.5 billion valuation. Investors The round was co-led by Kleiner Perkins and IVP, with participation from Salesforce Ventures, Datadog Ventures, and all existing investors, bringing Chainguard's total funding to $612 million. Kleiner Perkins is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redpanda Raises $100M in Series D at $1B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/redpanda-raises-100m-in-series-d-at-1b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Redpanda, a San Francisco, CA-based real-time data platform, has secured $100 million in Series D funding at a $1 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by GV, with participation from Lightspeed Venture Partners, bringing Redpanda’s total funding to $265 million. Founded in 2009, GV is Alphabet's venture capital arm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Runway Raises $308 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/runway-raises-308-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Runway, a New York-based startup developing a suite of generative AI models for media production, has raised $308 million in Series D funding. Investors General Atlantic led the Series D funding round, with participation from Fidelity Management & Research Company, Baillie Gifford, Nvidia, SoftBank, and others. This latest funding brings …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyberhaven Raises $100M in Series D at a $1B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cyberhaven-raises-100m-in-series-d-at-a-1b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyberhaven, a Palo Alto, CA-based AI-powered data security company, has raised $100 million in Series D funding, reaching a $1 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by StepStone Group, with participation from Schroders and Industry Ventures. This latest investment brings Cyberhaven's total funding to $250 million. StepStone Group, founded …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fleetio Raises Over $450 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/fleetio-raises-over-450-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fleetio, a Birmingham, Alabama-based fleet management and maintenance software company, has raised over $450 million in Series D funding. The company also announced the acquisition of Auto Integrate, a maintenance authorization platform, a combined business valued at $1.5B+. Investors The funding round was co-led by Elephant and Growth Equity at …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pentera Raises $60 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/pentera-raises-60-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pentera, a Boston, MA-based company specializing in automated security validation solutions, has raised $60 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Evolution Equity Partners, with participation from Farallon Capital Management, bringing Pentera’s total funding to $250 million. Evolution Equity Partners is an international venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abridge Raises $250 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/abridge-raises-250-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abridge, a Pittsburgh, PA-based generative AI platform for clinical conversations, has raised $250 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was co-led by Elad Gil and IVP, with participation from Bessemer Venture Partners, California Health Care Foundation, CapitalG, CVS Health Ventures, K. Ventures, Lightspeed Venture Partners, NVentures (NVIDIA’s venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesia Raises $180 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/synthesia-raises-180-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Synthesia, a London, UK-based AI-powered video communications platform provider, has raised $180 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by NEA, with participation from existing investors including GV, MMC Ventures, and FirstMark, as well as new backers such as WiL (World Innovation Lab), Atlassian Ventures, and PSP …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Instabase Raises $100 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/instabase-raises-100-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Instabase, a San Francisco, California-based applied AI company specializing in unstructured data management, has raised $100 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by QIA, with participation from existing investors Greylock Partners, NEA, Andreessen Horowitz, and Index Ventures. Qatar Investment Authority (QIA) is the sovereign wealth fund …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Netradyne Raises $90 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/netradyne-raises-90-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Netradyne, a San Diego, CA-based SaaS provider specializing in AI and edge computing, has raised $90 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Point72 Private Investments, with additional participation from Qualcomm Ventures and Pavilion Capital. Point72 Private Investments is an institutional platform comprising Point72 Ventures, a …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Qventus Raises $105 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/qventus-raises-105-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Qventus, a Mountain View, CA-based provider of an AI-based care automation platform, has raised $105 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by KKR, with participation from Bessemer Venture Partners and strategic health system investors, including Northwestern Medicine, HonorHealth, and Allina Health. KKR is a global investment …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AMP Raises $91 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/amp-raises-91-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AMP, a Denver, Colorado-based company specializing in AI-driven sortation technology for the waste and recycling industry, has raised $91 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Congruent Ventures, with participation from Sequoia Capital, XN, Blue Earth Capital, Liberty Mutual Investments, CalSTRS, Wellington Management, Range Ventures, and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zopper Raises $25 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/zopper-raises-25-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zopper, a Noida, India-based insurance technology company, has raised $25 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Elevation Capital and Dharana Capital, with participation from existing investor Blume Ventures, as well as backing from Creaegis, Bessemer Venture Partners, and ICICI Venture. Elevation Capital is a venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyera Raises $300 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cyera-raises-300-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyera, a New York-based data security company, has raised $300 million in a Series D funding round, bringing its total funding to $760 million. Investors The round was led by Accel and Sapphire Ventures, with participation from Sequoia, Redpoint, Coatue, and Georgian, bringing Cyera's valuation to $3 billion. Accel is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cresta Raises $125 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cresta-raises-125-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cresta, a Palo Alto, CA-based provider of an end-to-end generative AI platform for contact centers, has raised $125 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by new investors World Innovation Lab (WiL) and QIA, with participation from Accenture, EnvisionX Capital, LG Technology Ventures, Qualcomm Ventures, and Workday …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tourlane Raises €25 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/tourlane-raises-25-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tourlane, a Berlin, Germany-based provider of an AI-driven platform for personalized multi-stop travel, has secured €25 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Sequoia Capital, with additional investments from Target Global, Jared Smith (Qualtrics co-founder), and HV Capital. Headquartered in Menlo Park, California, Sequoia Capital is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:56:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Armis Raises $200 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/armis-raises-200-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Armis, a San Francisco, CA-based cyber exposure management and security company, has raised $200 million in Series D funding, at a $4.2 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by General Catalyst and Alkeon Capital, with participation from Brookfield Technology Partners and Georgian. General Catalyst: A global investment and transformation …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Globality Raises $47 Million in Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/globality-raises-47-million-in-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Globality, a Palo Alto, CA-based provider of AI-driven sourcing and procurement solutions, has raised $47 million in Series D-1 and D-2 preferred stock offerings. Investors The funding round, backed by existing shareholders and new investors like Rollins Capital, brings the total capital raised by the company to $356 million. Globality …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zip Raises $190 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/zip-raises-190-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zip, a San Francisco, CA-based AI-powered procurement orchestration platform, has raised $190 million in Series D funding, bringing its valuation to $2.2 billion. Investors The round was led by BOND, with participation from DST Global, Adams Street, Alkeon, Y Combinator, and CRV. BOND is a global technology investment firm that …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suki Raises $70 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/suki-raises-70-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Suki, a Redwood City, CA-based provider of artificial intelligence (AI) solutions for the healthcare sector, has raised $70 million in Series D funding, bringing its total raised to $165 million. Investors The round was led by Hedosophia, with participation from Venrock, March Capital, Flare Capital, Breyer Capital, and inHealth Ventures. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UJET Raises $76 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ujet-raises-76-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[UJET, a San Francisco, CA-based provider of AI-powered cloud contact center solutions, has raised $76 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Sapphire Ventures, with participation from KeyCorp, IonPacific, and existing investors like GV, Kleiner Perkins, and Ericsson Ventures. Sapphire is a global venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Qure.ai Secures $65 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/qure-ai-secures-65-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Qure.ai, an India-based healthtech company specializing in AI-driven solutions for early disease detection, has secured $65 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by Lightspeed Venture Partners and 360 ONE Asset Management. Merck’s Global Health Innovation Fund, Kae Capital, and existing investors, including Novo Holdings participated. Lightspeed …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oyster Raises $59 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/oyster-raises-59-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oyster, a San Francisco, CA-based global employment solution to employ, pay, and care for distributed teams, has raised $59 million in Series D funding at a $1.2 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Silver Lake Waterman, with participation from existing investors Emergence Capital, Stripes, Georgian, G2 Venture Partners, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:00 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EliseAI Secures $75 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/eliseai-secures-75-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[EliseAI, a New York-based technology company specializing in conversational AI platforms for the housing industry, has secured $75 million in Series D funding at a $1 billion valuation. Investors The funding round was led by Sapphire Ventures, with participation from existing investors including Navitas Capital, Point72 Private Investments, DivcoWest Ventures, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Levitate Secures $15 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/levitate-secures-15-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Levitate, a Raleigh, NC-based SaaS 'Happiness Platform' for relationship-based businesses, has secured $15 million in Series D funding. The company also announced the general availability of a suite of tools for helping businesses manage their online presence. Newly launched features include website design, Google Review management, and blog content creation, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abnormal Security Closes $250 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/abnormal-security-closes-250-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abnormal Security, a San Francisco, CA-based cybersecurity company specializing in AI-native human behavior security, has closed $250 million in Series D funding at a $5.1 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Wellington Management, with participation from Greylock Partners, Menlo Ventures, Insight Partners, and CrowdStrike Falcon Fund. This brings …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seeq Closes $50 Million in Series D Round]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/seeq-closes-50-million-in-series-d-round</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seeq, a Seattle, Washington-based industrial analytics, AI, and monitoring company, has closed a $50 million Series D funding round, bringing its total funding to approximately $165 million. Investors The round was led by Sixth Street Growth, a leading global investment firm, with participation from existing investors including Insight Partners, Altira …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cohere Raises $500 Million at $5.5B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cohere-raises-500-million-at-5-5-b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cohere, a Toronto, Canada-based generative AI startup, has raised $500 million in Series D funding, at a $5.5 billion valuation. Investors The investment came from investors such as Cisco, AMD, and Fujitsu. This round also included participation from Canadian pension investment manager PSP Investments and Canada’s export credit agency EDC, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Huma Raises Over $80 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/huma-raises-over-80-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Huma, a London and New York-based global healthcare AI company, has raised over $80 million in Series D funding, bringing its total funding to $300 million. The company also announced the launch of its Huma Cloud Platform. The platform offers no-code configuration for regulated disease management tools across therapeutic areas, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Formation Bio Raises $372 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/formation-bio-raises-372-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Formation Bio, a New York-based tech-driven and AI-native pharma company, raised $372 million in Series D financing. Investors The funding round was led by Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), with participation from Sanofi and existing investors such as Sequoia, Thrive Capital, Emerson Collective, and Lachy Groom. New investors, including SV Angel Growth …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Huntress Secures $150 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/huntress-secures-150-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Huntress, a Columbia, MD-based cybersecurity company for small businesses and the service providers that support them, secured a $150 million Series D funding round. Investors The round was led by Kleiner Perkins, Meritech Capital, and existing investor Sapphire Ventures. Founded in 1972, Kleiner Perkins is a venture capital firm based …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ramp Raises $150 Million in Series D-2 Round]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ramp-raises-150-million-in-series-d-2-round</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ramp, a New York-based spend management startup, has raised $150 million in Series D-2 funding at a post-money valuation of $7.65 billion. Investors Khosla Ventures and Founders Fund co-led the round. Other participants included Sequoia Capital, Greylock, 8VC, Thrive Capital, General Catalyst, Sands Capital, D1 Capital, Lux Capital, Iconiq Capital, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pigment Raises $145 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/pigment-raises-145-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pigment, a Paris, France-based business planning platform startup, has raised $145 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by ICONIQ Growth, with participation from Sandberg Bernthal Venture Partners, as well as several other existing investors including IVP, Meritech, Greenoaks, and Felix Capital. ICONIQ Growth is a venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coro Secures $100 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/coro-secures-100-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coro, a New York-based cybersecurity platform specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), has secured $100 million in Series D funding. Investors The round was led by One Peak, with participation from existing investors Energy Impact Partners and Balderton Capital. This funding round brings Coro's total funds raised to …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mews Secures $110 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/mews-secures-110-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mews, a Prague, Czech Republic-based startup specializing in hotel IT management tools, has secured $110 million in Series D funding, valuing the company at $1.2 billion. SaaS Investors The round was led by Kinnevik, with participation from Kinnevik, Revaia, Goldman Sachs Alternatives, Notion Capital, and LGVP. Founded in 1936, Kinnevik …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capillary Technologies Raises $95M in Series D Extension]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/capillary-technologies-raises-95m-in-series-d-extension</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capillary Technologies, a Singapore-based SaaS startup, raised $95 million in funding, bringing its Series D funding round to $140 million. The company raised $45 million in the initial Series D round in June last year. SaaS Investors The round was led by Avataar Venture Partners. Other investors include Pantheon Ventures, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glean Secures Over $200 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/glean-secures-over-200-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glean, a Palo, Alto, CA-based AI-driven work assistant, has secured over $200 million in Series D funding, reaching a valuation of $2.2 billion. SaaS Investors Led by Kleiner Perkins and Lightspeed Venture Partners, with support from various investors including Sequoia Capital and Coatue. Founded in 1972, Kleiner Perkins is a …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:03 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clumio Secures $75 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/clumio-secures-75-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clumio, a Santa Clara, CA-based data backup and recovery provider for companies using the public cloud, has secured $75 million in Series D funding. SaaS Investors The round was led by Sutter Hill Ventures, with participation from Index Ventures, Altimeter Capital, and NewView Capital. Founded in 1962, Sutter Hill Ventures …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silverfort Raises $116 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/silverfort-raises-116-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silverfort, a Tel Aviv, Israel- and Boston, MA-based identity protection company, has raised $116 million in Series D funding, bringing its total amount raised to $222 million. SaaS Investors The round was led by Brighton Park Capital (BPC), with participation from existing investors including Acrew Capital, Greenfield Partners, Citi Ventures, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vestwell Raises $125 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/vestwell-raises-125-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vestwell, a Manhattan, New York-based company providing infrastructure for employers to power workplace savings programs, has raised $125 million in funding. SaaS Investors The round was led by Lightspeed Venture Partners. Existing investors Fin Capital, Primary Venture Partners, and FinTech Collective participated, along with new investors Blue Owl and HarbourVest. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meniga Raises €15 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/meniga-raises-15-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meniga, a London, UK-based personal financial management provider, raised €15 million in Series D funding, bringing its total raised of €55 million in funding to date. SaaS Investors The investment round includes major European banks Groupe BPCE and Crédito Agrícola, along with Icelandic VC group Omega ehf. Groupe BPCE is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enable Raises $120 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/enable-raises-120-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enable, a San Francisco, CA-based startup that sells rebate software to trading partners, raised $120 million in a Series D funding round that values the company at $1 billion pre-money. SaaS Investors The funding round was led by Lightspeed Venture Partners, with participation from all the previous lead investors including …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stampli Raises $61 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/stampli-raises-61-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stampli, a Mountain View, CA-based AI-powered accounts payable automation, raised $61 million in Series D funding, bringing its total amount raised to over $148 million. SaaS Investors The round was led by funds managed by Blackstone, with participation from existing investors Insight Partners, SignalFire, Bloomberg Beta, and NextWorld Capital. Blackstone …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perfios Raises $229 Million in Series D]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/perfios-raises-229-million-in-series-d</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perfios, a Bangalore, India-based SaaS Business-to-Business (B2B) software provider for financial institutions, raised $229 million in its Series D funding round SaaS Investors This funding was secured from private equity firm Kedaara Capital through a combination of primary fundraising and a secondary sale of shares. Kedaara Capital is an operationally …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:57:04 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
