<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS News – SERIES-B</title>
    <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com</link>
    <description>Funding news for SERIES-B</description>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CloudSEK Secures $10M Series B2]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cloudsek-secures-10m-series-b2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CloudSEK, a Bengaluru, India, and New Haven, Conn.-based predictive cyber threat intelligence firm specializing in AI-powered attack detection, has secured a $10 million Series B2 investment. Investors The round was led by Connecticut Innovations, with previous participation from Commvault, MassMutual Ventures, Inflexor Ventures, Prana Ventures, and Tenacity Ventures. Connecticut Innovations …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GovDash Raises $30 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/govdash-raises-30-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[GovDash, a New York-based AI-powered capture, proposal, and contract management platform, has raised $30 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Mucker Capital and British Columbia Investment Management Corporation (BCI), with participation from existing investors Northzone and Y Combinator. Mucker Capital is a top-rated venture firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aikido Security Raises $60M Series B at $1B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/aikido-security-raises-60m-series-b-at-1b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aikido Security, a Brussels, Belgium–based cybersecurity company, has raised $60 million in a Series B round at a $1 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by DST Global, with participation from PSG Equity. DST Global is a growth-equity investment firm specializing in late-stage, high-growth internet and technology companies. Founded …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defense Unicorns Secures $136M Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/defense-unicorns-secures-136m-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Defense Unicorns, a San Antonio, Texas–based defense technology company, has raised $136 million in a Series B funding round at a valuation exceeding $1 billion. Investors The round was led by Bain Capital, with participation from Ansa Capital, Sapphire Ventures, Valor Equity Partners, AVP, Uncorrelated Ventures, and former CIA Director …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MontyCloud Raises Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/montycloud-raises-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MontyCloud, a Seattle, WA–based autonomous cloud operations company, has raised a Series B funding round. Investors The round was led by Riverside Acceleration Capital, with participation from Lytical Ventures, S3 Ventures, Madrona Venture Group, and Raptor Group. Riverside Acceleration Capital (RAC) supports B2B software companies through two strategies: RAC Growth …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biller Genie Raises $22 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/biller-genie-raises-22-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biller Genie, an Orlando, FL–based fintech company that provides a cloud-based accounts receivable (AR) automation platform for SMBs, has raised $22 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Radian Capital, with participation from existing investors. Founded in 2016, Radian Capital is a New York–based growth equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Articul8 AI Raises Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/articul8-ai-raises-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Articul8 AI, a Santa Clara, CA–based enterprise GenAI software company, has closed the first tranche of its Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Adara Ventures, with participation from NXC Corporation, Aditya Birla Ventures, and other strategic investors. Adara Ventures is a European venture capital firm that specializes …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rewaa Raises $45 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/rewaa-raises-45-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rewaa, a Saudi Arabia-based retail technology company that provides a cloud-based platform for SMEs, has closed a $45 million Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Wa’ed Ventures, Idrisi Ventures, and Unity Ventures, with participation from Vision Ventures, RZM Investments, Sedco Capital, Saned Partners, Palm Ventures, and Abdulrahman …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kargo Raises $42 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/kargo-raises-42-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kargo, a San Francisco, CA-based industrial AI company for supply chain and logistics, has raised $42 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Avenir, with participation from Linse Capital, Hearst Ventures, Lightbank, and previous investors Matter Venture Partners and Sozo Ventures. Avenir is a growth equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manifold Raises $18 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/manifold-raises-18-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Manifold, a Newton, Massachusetts–based AI platform for the life sciences, has raised $18 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Reach Capital, with participation from SilverArc Capital, Industry Ventures, and existing investors TQ Ventures and Calibrate Ventures. Reach Capital is a San Francisco–based venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virohan Raises $7.5 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/virohan-raises-7-5-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Virohan, a New Delhi, India-based healthcare education platform, has raised INR 65 crore ($7.5 million) in its ongoing Series B funding round. Investors The round was led by Mynavi Corporation, with participation from Blume Ventures, Bharat Inclusive Technologies Seed Fund, and Rebright Partners. Established on August 15, 1973, Mynavi Corporation …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lovable Raises $330M Series B at $6.6B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/lovable-raises-330m-series-b-at-6-6b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lovable, a Stockholm, Sweden-based AI startup that streamlines software development, has raised $330 million in Series B funding at a $6.6 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by CapitalG and Menlo Ventures’ Anthology Fund, with participation from NVentures (NVIDIA), Salesforce Ventures, Databricks Ventures, T.Capital (Deutsche Telekom), Atlassian Ventures, HubSpot …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ben Secures $27.5 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ben-secures-27-5-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ben, a London, UK-based AI-native employee benefits platform designed for global enterprises, has secured $27.5 million (£20.8M) in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Mercia Ventures, with participation from Atomico, Cherry Ventures, DN Capital, Seedcamp, and new backing from QuantumLight Capital. Mercia Ventures is one of the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Axion Raises $37 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/axion-raises-37-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Axion, a New York–based AI platform for manufacturing product quality, has raised $37 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Salesforce Ventures, with participation from Bessemer Venture Partners, Schneider Electric Ventures, and existing investors. Salesforce Ventures is the corporate venture capital (CVC) arm of Salesforce, the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:59:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
