<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS News – SERIES-C</title>
    <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com</link>
    <description>Funding news for SERIES-C</description>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Xoxoday Raises Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/xoxoday-raises-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Xoxoday, a Bengaluru, India–based global rewards, incentives, and loyalty technology company, has raised a Series C funding round. Investors The round was backed by existing investors Apis Partners and 57 Stars. Apis Partners is a London-based global private equity and growth investment firm that specializes in financial services and technology …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Luxury Presence Secures $37 Million in Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/luxury-presence-secures-37-million-in-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Luxury Presence, an Austin, Texas–based growth platform designed for real estate agents, teams, and brokerages, has secured $37 million in funding. Investors The funding includes $22 million in Series C equity financing, led by Bessemer Venture Partners, with participation from NextEquity, GSBackers, TPC, and Adam and Jade Mills, along with …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Swap Raises $100 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/swap-raises-100-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Swap, a New York–based AI-driven, end-to-end commerce operating system, has raised $100 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was co-led by DST Global and ICONIQ, with ICONIQ doubling down on its prior investment. DST Global is a growth equity and venture capital firm specializing in late-stage investments in …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moonshot AI Raises $500M Series C at $4.3B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/moonshot-ai-raises-500m-series-c-at-4-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Moonshot AI, a Beijing, China-based artificial intelligence company, has raised $500 million in a Series C round, boosting its valuation to $4.3 billion. Investors The round was led by IDG Capital, with participation from existing investors Alibaba Group Holding and Tencent Holdings. IDG Capital is a global investment powerhouse and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Concept Raises $100 Million Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/neural-concept-raises-100-million-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural Concept, a Lausanne, Switzerland–based AI platform and engineering intelligence for product development, has raised $100 million in a Series C funding round. Investors The round was led by Growth Equity at Goldman Sachs Alternatives, with participation from existing investors Forestay Capital, Alven, HTGF, D.E. Shaw Ventures, and Aster Capital. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Codoxo Raises $35 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/codoxo-raises-35-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Codoxo, a Duluth, Georgia-based provider of AI and generative AI-powered healthcare payment integrity solutions, has raised $35 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by CVS Health Ventures, with participation from Echo Health Ventures, Sands Capital, 111 West Capital, Brewer Lane Ventures, Wipro Ventures, 450 Ventures, and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Canary Secures ¥4 Billion Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/canary-secures-4-billion-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canary, a Tokyo, Japan-based company developing vertical AI solutions for the real estate industry, has secured approximately ¥4 billion ($30.1M) in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by Angel Bridge, with participation from new investors including WiL and Mizuho Capital. Angel Bridge Co., Ltd. is a Tokyo-based venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:39 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fact Base Lands ¥4.4 Billion in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/fact-base-lands-4-4-billion-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fact Base, a Tokyo, Japan-based SaaS startup for the manufacturing industry, has raised ¥4.4 billion in Series C funding. Investors The round was backed by Insight Partners, marking its first-ever investment in a Japanese startup. Insight Partners is a global software investor that partners with high-growth technology, software, and internet …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AITRICS Secures KRW 35 Billion in Series C Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/aitrics-secures-krw-35-billion-in-series-c-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AITRICS, a Seoul, South Korea–based AI technology company, has secured 35 billion won ($23.7M) in Series C funding, bringing its total raised to 73.1 billion won. Investors Nine Korean and international venture capital firms and financial institutions participated in the round, including Premier Partners, Hanriver Partners, Mirae Asset Venture Investment, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Range Raises $60 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/range-raises-60-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Range, a McLean, VA–based AI-powered wealth management platform, has raised $60 million in Series C funding, bringing its total capital raised to over $100 million. Investors The round was led by Scale Venture Partners, with participation from Gradient Ventures, Cathay Innovation, and new investors including 53 Stations. Scale Venture Partners …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Doppel Raises $70 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/doppel-raises-70-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Doppel, a San Francisco, CA-based AI-native social engineering defense platform, has raised $70 million in Series C funding, bringing its total funding to $124 million. Investors The round was led by Bessemer Venture Partners, with participation from George Kurtz (CrowdStrike), NTT DOCOMO Ventures, Aurum Partners, the a16z Cultural Leadership Fund, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suno Raises $250M Series C at a $2.45B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/suno-raises-250m-series-c-at-a-2-45b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Suno, a Cambridge, MA-based AI-powered music creation platform, has raised $250 million in Series C funding at a $2.45B post-money valuation. Investors The round was led by Menlo Ventures, with participation from NVentures (NVIDIA’s venture capital arm), Hallwood Media, Lightspeed, and Matrix. Menlo Ventures is a venture capital firm based …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Luma AI Raises $900 Million Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/luma-ai-raises-900-million-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Luma AI, a San Francisco, CA–based artificial intelligence company building multimodal AGI, has raised $900 million in a Series C funding round. Investors The round was led by HUMAIN, with significant participation from AMD Ventures and existing investors Andreessen Horowitz, Amplify Partners, and Matrix Partners. HUMAIN, a PIF company, is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lisse Adds ¥1 Billion in Series C Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/lisse-adds-1-billion-in-series-c-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lisse, a Tokyo, Japan-based legal tech company, has raised ¥1 billion in the second close of its Series C funding round. Investors Four new investors joined the round: Japan Post Spiral Regional Innovation Fund, NTT Docomo Ventures, Aozora Corporate Investment, and SB C&S, along with financial institutions providing additional financing. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:41 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CoLab Raises $72 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/colab-raises-72-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CoLab, a Canada-based company building an AI-powered EngineeringOS for hardware and engineering teams, has raised $72 million USD in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by Intrepid Growth Partners, with participation from existing investors Insight Partners, Y Combinator, Pelorus VC, Killick Capital, and Spider Capital. Intrepid Growth Partners …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scribe Raises $75M Series C at $1.3B valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/scribe-raises-75m-series-c-at-1-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Scribe, a San Francisco, CA–based provider of a workflow AI platform that creates step-by-step guides for any process or software, has raised $75 million in a Series C round at a $1.3 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by StepStone, with participation from Amplify Partners, Redpoint Ventures, Tiger Global, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Legora Raises $150 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/legora-raises-150-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Legora, a New York–based collaborative AI platform for lawyers, has raised $150 million in a Series C round at a $1.8 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Bessemer Venture Partners, with participation from existing investors ICONIQ, General Catalyst, Redpoint Ventures, Benchmark, and Y Combinator. Bessemer Venture Partners is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shippio Raises ¥3.24 Billion in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/shippio-raises-3-24-billion-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shippio, a Tokyo-based digital trade and logistics platform, has raised a total of ¥3.24 billion in Series C funding, bringing its total raised to approximately ¥7 billion. The round combines both equity and debt financing. Investors The equity portion (¥1.87 billion) was led by DNX Ventures, with participation from Energy …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sublime Security Raises $150 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/sublime-security-raises-150-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sublime Security, a Washington, D.C.–based agentic email security platform, has raised $150 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by Georgian, with participation from new investors Avenir and 01A, as well as existing backers Index Ventures, IVP, Citi Ventures, and Slow Ventures. Georgian is a Toronto-based venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nava Benefits Secures $30 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/nava-benefits-secures-30-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nava Benefits, a New York–based benefits brokerage aiming to fix healthcare, has secured $30 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by Thrive Capital, with participation from Glynn Capital, GV, Quiet Capital, Gaingels, People Tech Partners, Fenwick, Alumni Ventures, and Pascal Ventures. Founded in 2009, Thrive Capital …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Findem Raises $51 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/findem-raises-51-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Findem, a Redwood City, CA-based AI-powered talent acquisition and management platform, has secured $51 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by SLW, with participation from Wing Ventures, Harmony Capital, Four Rivers Group, and growth financing from J.P. Morgan. Founded in 2012 as Silver Lake Waterman, SLW …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:42 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anrok Raises $55 Million Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/anrok-raises-55-million-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anrok, a San Francisco, CA-based global sales tax compliance platform for digital businesses, has raised $55 million in Series C funding, bringing its total funding to over $100 million. Investors The round was led by Spark Capital, with participation from Sapphire Ventures and existing investors Khosla Ventures, Sequoia Capital, and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kojo Raises $10M Series C Extension]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/kojo-raises-10m-series-c-extension</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kojo, a San Francisco, CA-based construction procurement and materials management platform, has raised $10 million in a Series C extension. Investors The extension round was led by Wesco International, joining existing Series C investors including Battery Ventures, 8VC, Schneider Electric, RXR, Suffolk Construction, Human Capital, and BoxGroup. Wesco International is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dexory Raises $165 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/dexory-raises-165-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dexory, a London, UK-based robotics and AI startup specializing in real-time warehouse intelligence, has raised $165 million in a Series C funding round. Investors The round was led by Eurazeo’s Growth team, with participation from LTS Growth, Endeavor Catalyst, and existing investors DTCP, Atomico, Lakestar, Elaia, Latitude Ventures, Wave-X, and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[n8n Raises $180M Series C at $2.5B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/n8n-raises-180m-series-c-at-2-5b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[n8n, a Berlin, Germany-based AI businesses automation startup, has raised $180 million in a Series C round, valuing the company at $2.5 billion. Investors The round was led by Accel, with participation from Meritech, Redpoint, Evantic, Visionaries Club, T Capital, NVentures, and follow-on investments from Sequoia, HV Capital, Highland Europe, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ClickHouse Extends Series C Funding Round]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/clickhouse-extends-series-c-funding-round</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ClickHouse, a San Francisco, CA-based open-source columnar database management system, has extended its Series C funding round. Investors New investors include Citi Ventures, Insight Partners, Peak XV Partners, Founders Circle Capital, D. E. Shaw Ventures, Adams Street Partners, Rosberg Ventures, Expanding Capital, and individuals such as Brock Purdy, Christian McCaffrey, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Filigran Secures $58 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/filigran-secures-58-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Filigran, a Paris, France-based cybersecurity startup specializing in extended threat management, has secured $58 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was supported by Eurazeo, Insight Partners, Accel, and Deutsche Telekom (T.Capital). Filigran Use of Funds The company will use the funding to accelerate product development, expand into new …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Petpooja Raises $15.5 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/petpooja-raises-15-5-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Petpooja, an India-based restaurant point-of-sale (POS) and management software provider, has raised INR 137 crore (~USD 15.5 million) in a Series C funding round. Investors The round was led by Dharana Capital, with participation from Ashish Gupta (co-founder of Helion Ventures), as well as Urban Company’s founders, Abhiraj Singh Bhal, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:44 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fetcherr Raises $42 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/fetcherr-raises-42-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fetcherr, a Tel Aviv, Israel–based generative AI company, has raised $42 million in a Series C funding round. Investors The round was led by Salesforce Ventures, with participation from Battery Ventures, Left Lane Capital, and M-Fund. Salesforce Ventures is the corporate venture capital (CVC) arm of Salesforce, the global cloud-based …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SEON Raises $80 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/seon-raises-80-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SEON, an Austin, Texas- and Budapest, Hungary-based fraud prevention and AML compliance company, has raised $80 million in Series C funding, bringing its total funding to $187 million. Investors The round was led by Sixth Street Growth, with participation from IVP, Creandum, Firebolt, and new investor Hearst. Sixth Street Growth …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DRUID AI Raises $31 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/druid-ai-raises-31-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DRUID AI, a New York-based enterprise agentic AI company, has raised $31 million in a Series C funding round. Investors The round was led by Cipio Partners, with participation from TQ Ventures, Karma Ventures, Smedvig, and Hoxton Ventures. Cipio Partners is a European private equity and venture capital firm specializing …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Replit Raises $250 Million at $3B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/replit-raises-250-million-at-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Replit, a Foster City, CA-based agentic AI software creation platform, has raised $250 million in Series C funding, valuing the company at $3 billion. Investors The round was led by Prysm Capital, with participation from Amex Ventures, Google’s AI Futures Fund, YC, Craft, a16z, Coatue, Paul Graham, and others. Prysm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shift5 Raises $75 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/shift5-raises-75-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shift5, a Rosslyn, Virginia-based operational intelligence platform for defense and transportation systems, has raised $75 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by Hedosophia, with participation from Insight Partners, Center 15 Capital, 645 Ventures, Moore Strategic Ventures, Booz Allen Ventures, Squadra Ventures, AE Industrial, Disruptive, CSP Equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kapital Secures $100M Series C at $1.3B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/kapital-secures-100m-series-c-at-1-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kapital, a Mexico-based AI-driven platform for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in Latin America, has secured up to $100 million in a Series C round at a $1.3 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Tribe Capital and co-led by Pelion Ventures, with participation from Y Combinator, Marbruck Ventures, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You.com Raises $100M Series C at a $1.5B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/you-com-raises-100m-series-c-at-a-1-5b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[You.com, a Palo Alto, CA–based AI startup, has raised $100 million in Series C funding at a $1.5 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by Cox Enterprises, with participation from existing investors Georgian, Salesforce Ventures, and Norwest. Cox Enterprises is a privately held global conglomerate headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:45 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ontic Raises $230 Million in Series C]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ontic-raises-230-million-in-series-c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ontic, an Austin, Texas-based connected security intelligence platform, has raised $230 million in Series C funding. Investors The round was led by KKR, with participation from JMI Equity, Silverton Partners, Ridge Ventures, and Ten Eleven Ventures. KKR is a global investment firm specializing in alternative asset management, capital markets, and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:01:46 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
