<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS News – SERIES-A</title>
    <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com</link>
    <description>Funding news for SERIES-A</description>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Depthfirst Raises $40 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/depthfirst-raises-40-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Depthfirst, a San Francisco, CA–based AI-powered security company, has raised $40 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Accel, with participation from Alt Capital, BoxGroup, Liquid 2 Ventures, Mantis VC, SV Angel, and prominent angel investors including Jeff Dean and Kirsten Green. Founded in 1983 and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coxwave Secures $5M Pre-Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/coxwave-secures-5m-pre-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coxwave, a Seoul, South Korea–based AI product analytics platform provider, has secured $5 million in Pre-Series A funding. Investors The round was led by L&S Venture Capital, with participation from KB Investment, Hyundai Venture Investment, Hyundai Motor Company’s ZERO1NE Ventures, and KDB Capital. L&S Venture Capital is a South Korean …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flip Raises $20 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/flip-raises-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flip, a New York–based AI platform automating enterprise customer service calls, has raised $20 million in Series A funding, bringing its total funding to $31 million. Investors The round was co-led by Next Coast Ventures and Ridge Ventures, with participation from Data Point Capital, ScOp Venture Capital, Bullpen Capital, Forum …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OurPetPolicy Closes $8 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ourpetpolicy-closes-8-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OurPetPolicy, a Boise, Idaho–based, AI-enabled animal and ESA management platform for rental housing operators, has raised $8 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by RET Ventures, with participation from StageDotO and Capital Eleven. RET Ventures is a venture capital firm actively shaping the future of the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISA Labs Raises $11.1 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/risa-labs-raises-11-1-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RISA Labs, a Palo Alto, California–based AI operating system for oncology, has raised $11.1 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was co-led by Cencora Ventures and Optum Ventures, with participation from Oncology Ventures, Z21 Ventures, and John Simon via Ventureforgood. Cencora Ventures is the corporate venture capital arm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protege Raises $30 Million Series A Extension]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/protege-raises-30-million-series-a-extension</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protege, a New York-based AI data platform, has raised $30 million in a Series A extension funding round, bringing its total funding to $65 million. Investors The extension round was led by Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), with returning investors including Footwork, CRV, Bloomberg Beta, Flex Capital, and Shaper Capital. Andreessen Horowitz …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prudentia Sciences Lands $20M in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/prudentia-sciences-lands-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prudentia Sciences, a Cambridge, MA–based AI-native platform for life sciences due diligence and dealmaking, has raised $20 million in a Series A round, bringing its total funding to $27 million. Investors The round was led by McKesson Ventures, with participation from SignalFire and existing investors Iaso Ventures, Virtue, and GV. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:48 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
