<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS News – SERIES-B</title>
    <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com</link>
    <description>Funding news for SERIES-B</description>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aikido Security Raises $60M Series B at $1B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/aikido-security-raises-60m-series-b-at-1b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aikido Security, a Brussels, Belgium–based cybersecurity company, has raised $60 million in a Series B round at a $1 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by DST Global, with participation from PSG Equity. DST Global is a growth-equity investment firm specializing in late-stage, high-growth internet and technology companies. Founded …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MontyCloud Raises Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/montycloud-raises-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MontyCloud, a Seattle, WA–based autonomous cloud operations company, has raised a Series B funding round. Investors The round was led by Riverside Acceleration Capital, with participation from Lytical Ventures, S3 Ventures, Madrona Venture Group, and Raptor Group. Riverside Acceleration Capital (RAC) supports B2B software companies through two strategies: RAC Growth …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defense Unicorns Secures $136M Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/defense-unicorns-secures-136m-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Defense Unicorns, a San Antonio, Texas–based defense technology company, has raised $136 million in a Series B funding round at a valuation exceeding $1 billion. Investors The round was led by Bain Capital, with participation from Ansa Capital, Sapphire Ventures, Valor Equity Partners, AVP, Uncorrelated Ventures, and former CIA Director …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biller Genie Raises $22 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/biller-genie-raises-22-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biller Genie, an Orlando, FL–based fintech company that provides a cloud-based accounts receivable (AR) automation platform for SMBs, has raised $22 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Radian Capital, with participation from existing investors. Founded in 2016, Radian Capital is a New York–based growth equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Articul8 AI Raises Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/articul8-ai-raises-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Articul8 AI, a Santa Clara, CA–based enterprise GenAI software company, has closed the first tranche of its Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Adara Ventures, with participation from NXC Corporation, Aditya Birla Ventures, and other strategic investors. Adara Ventures is a European venture capital firm that specializes …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rewaa Raises $45 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/rewaa-raises-45-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rewaa, a Saudi Arabia-based retail technology company that provides a cloud-based platform for SMEs, has closed a $45 million Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Wa’ed Ventures, Idrisi Ventures, and Unity Ventures, with participation from Vision Ventures, RZM Investments, Sedco Capital, Saned Partners, Palm Ventures, and Abdulrahman …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kargo Raises $42 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/kargo-raises-42-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kargo, a San Francisco, CA-based industrial AI company for supply chain and logistics, has raised $42 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Avenir, with participation from Linse Capital, Hearst Ventures, Lightbank, and previous investors Matter Venture Partners and Sozo Ventures. Avenir is a growth equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:49 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manifold Raises $18 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/manifold-raises-18-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Manifold, a Newton, Massachusetts–based AI platform for the life sciences, has raised $18 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Reach Capital, with participation from SilverArc Capital, Industry Ventures, and existing investors TQ Ventures and Calibrate Ventures. Reach Capital is a San Francisco–based venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virohan Raises $7.5 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/virohan-raises-7-5-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Virohan, a New Delhi, India-based healthcare education platform, has raised INR 65 crore ($7.5 million) in its ongoing Series B funding round. Investors The round was led by Mynavi Corporation, with participation from Blume Ventures, Bharat Inclusive Technologies Seed Fund, and Rebright Partners. Established on August 15, 1973, Mynavi Corporation …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lovable Raises $330M Series B at $6.6B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/lovable-raises-330m-series-b-at-6-6b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lovable, a Stockholm, Sweden-based AI startup that streamlines software development, has raised $330 million in Series B funding at a $6.6 billion valuation. Investors The round was led by CapitalG and Menlo Ventures’ Anthology Fund, with participation from NVentures (NVIDIA), Salesforce Ventures, Databricks Ventures, T.Capital (Deutsche Telekom), Atlassian Ventures, HubSpot …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive Security Raises $81 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/adaptive-security-raises-81-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adaptive Security, a New York-based provider of AI-powered social engineering prevention solutions, has raised $81 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Bain Capital Ventures, with participation from NVentures (NVIDIA), OpenAI Startup Fund, Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), Abstract Ventures, Capital One Ventures, and Citi Ventures. Bain Capital …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Axion Raises $37 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/axion-raises-37-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Axion, a New York–based AI platform for manufacturing product quality, has raised $37 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Salesforce Ventures, with participation from Bessemer Venture Partners, Schneider Electric Ventures, and existing investors. Salesforce Ventures is the corporate venture capital (CVC) arm of Salesforce, the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ben Secures $27.5 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ben-secures-27-5-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ben, a London, UK-based AI-native employee benefits platform designed for global enterprises, has secured $27.5 million (£20.8M) in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Mercia Ventures, with participation from Atomico, Cherry Ventures, DN Capital, Seedcamp, and new backing from QuantumLight Capital. Mercia Ventures is one of the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Logpresso Raises KRW 16 Billion Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/logpresso-raises-krw-16-billion-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Logpresso, a Seoul, South Korea–based cloud-native SIEM provider, has raised KRW 16 billion (approx. USD12M) in Series B funding. Investors The round included existing investors such as KB Investment, along with new institutional investors. To date, Logpresso has secured a total of KRW 23 billion (approximately USD 17 million) in …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:50 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Qargo Secures $33 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/qargo-secures-33-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Qargo, a London-based intelligent transport management system, has raised $33 million in a Series B round, bringing its total funding to $54 million. Investors The round was led by Sofina, alongside existing investors. Sofina is a Belgian investment company listed on Euronext Brussels. Its mission is to partner with leading …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ritten Secures $35 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ritten-secures-35-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ritten, a Philadelphia, PA-based AI-powered system of record for behavioral health providers, has secured $35 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Five Elms Capital, with participation from existing investors Threshold Ventures, 8VC, Bienville Capital, and others. Five Elms Capital is a growth investor in software …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SALESCORE Raises ¥1.15 Billion in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/salescore-raises-1-15-billion-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SALESCORE, a Tokyo, Japan-based company whose vision is to make the joy of achievement a natural part of life, has raised ¥1.15 billion (USD 6.4M) in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Nissay Capital, with participation from SMBC Venture Capital, Mitsubishi UFJ Capital, and Nippon Venture Capital. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Notta Raises ¥2.3 Billion in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/notta-raises-2-3-billion-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Notta, a Tokyo, Japan-based provider of AI-powered transcription and meeting note tool, has raised approximately ¥2.3 billion (USD 15M) in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Granite-Integral Capital Pte. Ltd., a joint venture between Granite Asia and Integral Group that focuses on investing in growth-stage technology companies, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Saviynt Raises $700M at Approximately $3B Valuation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/saviynt-raises-700m-at-approximately-3b-valuation</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Saviynt, a Los Angeles- and New York-based identity security company, has raised $700 million in a Series B funding at a valuation of approximately $3 billion. Investors The growth equity round was led by KKR, with participation from Sixth Street Growth, TenEleven, and existing investor Carrick Capital Partners. KKR is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outset Raises $30 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/outset-raises-30-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Outset, a San Francisco, CA-based AI-moderated research platform, has raised $30 million in Series B funding, bringing total funding to $51 million. Investors The round was led by Radical Ventures, with participation from M12 (Microsoft’s venture fund), Y Combinator, Adverb Ventures, and 8VC. Radical Ventures is a venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[401GO Secures $33 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/401go-secures-33-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[401GO, a Sandy, Utah-based fintech company that provides a fully owned 401(k) platform, has secured $33 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Centana Growth Partners, with participation from existing investors Next Frontier Capital, Rally Ventures, and Impression Ventures. Centana Growth Partners is a specialized growth …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:52 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crisp Raises $26 Million in Series B1]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/crisp-raises-26-million-in-series-b1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crisp, a Bentonville, Arkansas–based AI platform for retail data, has raised $26 million in a Series B1, bringing its total funding to $127 million. Investors The round was led by Paine Schwartz Partners, with participation from Blue Cloud Ventures, FirstMark Capital, Cox, DNX, Prologis, and Wellington Management. Paine Schwartz Partners …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assaia Raises $26.6 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/assaia-raises-26-6-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Assaia, a Zurich, Switzerland-based aviation technology company, has raised $26.6 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Armira Growth, with participation from existing investors. Armira Growth is a Germany-based growth equity firm that provides capital to tech-enabled companies across Europe, with a primary focus on the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Duve Raises $60 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/duve-raises-60-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Duve, a Tel Aviv, Israel–based AI-powered guest management platform, has raised $60 million in a Series B funding round, bringing its total capital raised to $85 million. Investors The round was led by Susquehanna Growth Equity, with participation from XT Venture Capital and other existing backers. Susquehanna Growth Equity (SGE) …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gradial Raises $35 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/gradial-raises-35-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gradial, a Seattle, Washington–based enterprise software company defining agentic marketing operations, has raised $35 million in Series B funding, bringing its total funding to $55 million. Investors The round was led by VMG Partners, with participation from existing investors Madrona and Pruven Capital. VMG Partners, founded in 2005 and based …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PermitFlow Raises $54 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/permitflow-raises-54-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PermitFlow, a New York-based AI platform for construction, has raised $54 million in a Series B round. Investors The round was led by Accel, with participation from Kleiner Perkins, Felicis, Initialized Capital, Altos Ventures, Y Combinator, and existing investors. Accel is a global venture capital firm that invests in early-stage …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BKN301 Extends Series B to €33 Million]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/bkn301-extends-series-b-to-33-million</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BKN301, a London, UK-based fintech architecture provider, has extended its Series B round to €33 million. The company also announced that it has acquired Planky, a UK-based technology firm specializing in AI-powered financial analytics and open banking solutions. Investors The latest financing includes a credit facility from funds and accounts …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Black Forest Labs Raises $300M in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/black-forest-labs-raises-300m-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Black Forest Labs, a Freiburg, Germany-based visual intelligence company, has raised $300M in Series B funding, valuing the company at $3.25 billion post-money. Investors The round was led by AMP and Salesforce Ventures, with participation from a wide group of returning and new institutional investors and angels. AMP is a …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overstory Raises $43 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/overstory-raises-43-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overstory, an Amsterdam, Netherlands-based company providing AI-powered vegetation intelligence, has raised $43 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Blume Equity, with participation from Energy Impact Partners and existing investors, including B Capital, Semapa Next, Pale Blue Dot, CapitalT, Convective Capital, Bentley Systems, MCJ, and Moxxie …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sorcero Raises $42.5 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/sorcero-raises-42-5-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sorcero, a Washington, D.C.-based AI-powered intelligence platform for life sciences, has raised $42.5 million in Series B financing. Investors The round was led by NewSpring Growth, with participation from Leawood Venture Capital and Blu Ventures. NewSpring Growth is the dedicated growth equity strategy of NewSpring Capital, a multi-strategy private equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sweet Security Raises $75 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/sweet-security-raises-75-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sweet Security, a Tel Aviv, Israel–based runtime CNAPP and AI security solutions provider, has raised $75 million in Series B funding, bringing its total funding to $120 million. Investors The round was led by Evolution Equity Partners, with participation from Munich Re Ventures, Glilot Capital Partners, and Key1 Capital. Evolution …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vyntelligence Raises $30 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/vyntelligence-raises-30-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vyntelligence, a London, UK-based agentic video intelligence platform for frontline work, has raised $30 million in Series B funding. Investors The round was co-led by Blume Equity and Morgan Stanley Investment Management’s 1GT climate private equity strategy. Blume Equity is a European climate-tech growth equity firm based in London and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genspark Raises $275 Million in Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/genspark-raises-275-million-in-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genspark, a Palo Alto, CA-based technology company, has closed an oversubscribed $275 million Series B financing at a $1.25 billion post-money valuation. The company also launched its AI Workspace, a platform designed to deliver fully autonomous business outcomes. Investors The oversubscribed round was led by Emergence Capital, with participation from …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Numeric Secures $51 Million Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/numeric-secures-51-million-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Numeric, a San Francisco, CA–based AI accounting automation platform, has secured $51 million in Series B funding, bringing its total funding to $89 million. Alongside the funding announcement, Numeric is launching its cash management product. Investors The round was led by IVP, with participation from Menlo Ventures, Founders Fund, Alkeon, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stylework Raises ₹30 Cr in Pre-Series B]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/stylework-raises-30-cr-in-pre-series-b</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stylework, a Gurugram-based flexible workspace platform in India, has raised ₹30 crore ($3.4M) in pre-Series B funding. Investors The round was led by Equentis Angel Fund, with participation from Karekeba Ventures, Cogniphy AIF Fund, LetsVenture Fund, and MoneyVyapaar. Equentis Angel Fund is a Category I Alternative Investment Fund in India, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:53:56 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
