<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS News – SERIES-A</title>
    <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com</link>
    <description>Funding news for SERIES-A</description>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISA Labs Raises $11.1 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/risa-labs-raises-11-1-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RISA Labs, a Palo Alto, California–based AI operating system for oncology, has raised $11.1 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was co-led by Cencora Ventures and Optum Ventures, with participation from Oncology Ventures, Z21 Ventures, and John Simon via Ventureforgood. Cencora Ventures is the corporate venture capital arm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OurPetPolicy Closes $8 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ourpetpolicy-closes-8-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OurPetPolicy, a Boise, Idaho–based, AI-enabled animal and ESA management platform for rental housing operators, has raised $8 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by RET Ventures, with participation from StageDotO and Capital Eleven. RET Ventures is a venture capital firm actively shaping the future of the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flip Raises $20 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/flip-raises-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flip, a New York–based AI platform automating enterprise customer service calls, has raised $20 million in Series A funding, bringing its total funding to $31 million. Investors The round was co-led by Next Coast Ventures and Ridge Ventures, with participation from Data Point Capital, ScOp Venture Capital, Bullpen Capital, Forum …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bluecopa Raises $7.5 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/bluecopa-raises-7-5-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bluecopa, a Hyderabad, India–based finance automation startup, has raised $7.5 million in a Series A funding round, bringing its total funding to $11.6 million. Investors The round was led by Analog Partners, with participation from existing investors Blume Ventures and Dallas Venture Capital. Analog Partners is a Singapore-based growth equity …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protege Raises $30 Million Series A Extension]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/protege-raises-30-million-series-a-extension</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protege, a New York-based AI data platform, has raised $30 million in a Series A extension funding round, bringing its total funding to $65 million. Investors The extension round was led by Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), with returning investors including Footwork, CRV, Bloomberg Beta, Flex Capital, and Shaper Capital. Andreessen Horowitz …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prudentia Sciences Lands $20M in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/prudentia-sciences-lands-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prudentia Sciences, a Cambridge, MA–based AI-native platform for life sciences due diligence and dealmaking, has raised $20 million in a Series A round, bringing its total funding to $27 million. Investors The round was led by McKesson Ventures, with participation from SignalFire and existing investors Iaso Ventures, Virtue, and GV. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trybe Raises $30 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/trybe-raises-30-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trybe, a London, UK–based provider of spa, bathhouse, leisure, and activity management software, has raised $30 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Five Elms Capital, a growth investor in software businesses that users love, providing capital and resources to help companies accelerate growth and strengthen …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:53 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spangle AI Raises $15 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/spangle-ai-raises-15-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spangle AI, a Seattle, Washington–based commerce-focused agentic infrastructure platform, has raised $15 million in a Series A round. Investors The round was led by NewRoad Capital Partners, with participation from Madrona, DNX Ventures, Streamlined Ventures, and strategic angel investors, bringing the company’s total funding to $21 million. NewRoad Capital Partners …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SUPWAT Bags ¥200M in Pre-Series A Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/supwat-bags-200m-in-pre-series-a-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SUPWAT, a Tokyo, Japan-based DX startup developing a SaaS tool for manufacturing, has raised approximately ¥200 million in a pre-Series A round. Investors The round was led by INSPiRE Mutualistic Symbiosis Fund 1, a Japanese venture capital and buyout fund managed by Inspire Investment Inc., which aims to bridge the …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAIA Technology Raises £4 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/maia-technology-raises-4-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MAIA Technology, a London, UK–based software company that provides portfolio management solutions, has raised £4 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Molten Ventures, with Mountside Ventures advising MAIA on the fundraise. Molten Ventures is a venture capital firm focused on investing in high-growth technology companies …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dwilar Raises ¥150 Million Pre-Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/dwilar-raises-150-million-pre-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dwilar, a Palo Alto, CA-based company developing an AI SaaS for credit assessment for foreigners, has raised ¥150 million in a pre-Series A funding round. Investors The round included existing shareholder 9 Capital, new investors MTG Ventures and Shinryo Fund, as well as several angel investors. Dwilar Use of Funds …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tucuvi Raises $20 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/tucuvi-raises-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tucuvi, a New York-based AI care management platform provider, has raised $20 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Cathay Innovation and Leadwind, with participation from existing investors Frontline Ventures, Seaya Ventures, and Shilling. Cathay Innovation is a multistage venture capital firm affiliated with Cathay Capital, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitro Commerce Raises $5 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/nitro-commerce-raises-5-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitro Commerce, a Gurugram, India–based AI-driven marketing automation startup, has raised USD $5 million in a Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Cornerstone Ventures, with participation from India Accelerator & Finvolve, Equentis Wealth Advisory Services, Grand Anicut Angel Fund, Razorpay Ventures, Rukum Sitara Fund, and Ankurit …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LMArena Raises $150 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/lmarena-raises-150-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[LMArena, a San Francisco, California–based AI evaluation startup, has raised $150 million in Series A funding, reaching a post-money valuation of $1.7 billion. Investors The round was led by Felicis and UC Investments, with participation from Andreessen Horowitz, The House Fund, LDVP, Kleiner Perkins, Lightspeed Venture Partners, and Laude Ventures. …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:54 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[H2 Corporation Raises Pre-Series A Extension]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/h2-corporation-raises-pre-series-a-extension</link>
            <description><![CDATA[H2 Corporation, a Toyo, Japan–based construction technology startup, has raised a pre-Series A extension round. Investors The round was led by New Enterprise Associates (NEA), with participation from existing investors Spiral Capital, JAFCO, MetaProp, One Capital, and Boost Capital. NEA is a global venture capital firm focused on helping entrepreneurs …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DataLane Raises $22.5 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/datalane-raises-22-5-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DataLane, a New York–based identity graph for local businesses, has raised $22.5 million in a Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Amplify Partners, with participation from Harry Stebbings, Basis Set, Mischief, and others, bringing DataLane’s total funding to $27 million. Amplify Partners, based in Menlo Park, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BriefCatch Raises $6 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/briefcatch-raises-6-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BriefCatch, an Arlington, Virginia–based AI-assisted legal writing platform for law firms and courts, has raised $6 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Full In, a software-focused growth equity firm specializing in founder-led software and B2B SaaS companies. Headquartered in New York, the firm primarily invests …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FINNY Raises $17 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/finny-raises-17-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[FINNY, a New York–based AI-powered prospecting and marketing platform for financial advisors, has secured a $17 million Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Venrock, with participation from William McNabb, Jason Wenk, Activant, Altruist, and returning investors including Y Combinator, Maple VC, and Crossbeam Ventures. Established in …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Galatek Raises $30 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/galatek-raises-30-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Galatek, a Singapore-based automation and artificial intelligence (AI) startup, has raised $30 million in a Series A funding round. Investors The Series A investors have not been disclosed. Galatek Use of Funds The company will use the funds to develop innovative products and expand local expertise in Europe, North America, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HEN Technologies Bags $22 Million in Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/hen-technologies-bags-22-million-in-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[HEN Technologies, a Hayward, California-based deep-tech company, has closed an oversubscribed $20 million Series A financing round, along with $2 million in venture debt. Investors The round was led by O’Neil Strategic Capital, with participation from NSFO, Tanas Capital, and Z21 Ventures, alongside $2 million in venture debt from Silicon …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cordulus Raises €6.8 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/cordulus-raises-6-8-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cordulus, a Denmark-based startup providing AI weather solutions, has raised €6.8 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Delphinus Venture Capital, with participation from Danish Agro, Rockstart, the Pajbjerg Foundation, and other private investors. Delphinus Venture Capital is a venture capital firm and investment fund headquartered …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:55 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GravityLabs Secures $17 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/gravitylabs-secures-17-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[GravityLabs, a South Korea-based AI-powered healthcare startup, has secured $17 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Goodwater Capital, with participation from SBVA (formerly SoftBank Ventures Asia), Atinum Investment, NAVER, DSC Investment, and Bass Ventures. Goodwater Capital is a Burlingame-based venture capital firm exclusively dedicated to …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ankar Raises $20 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/ankar-raises-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ankar, a London, UK-based startup that uses AI to streamline the process of obtaining and managing patents, has secured $20 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Atomico, with participation from Index Ventures, Norrsken, and Daphni, bringing Ankar's total funding to $24 million. Atomico is a …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluency Raises $40 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/fluency-raises-40-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluency, a Burlington, Vermont–based digital advertising operating system for scaling paid media operations across all major channels, has raised $40 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led and fully funded by Integrity Growth Partners, a growth equity firm focused on founder-led, bootstrapped technology companies. Based in Los …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Echo Raises $35 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/echo-raises-35-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Echo, a Tel Aviv, Israel–based AI-powered secure software infrastructure company, has raised $35 million in Series A funding, bringing its total funding to $50 million. Investors The round was led by N47, with participation from Notable Capital, Hyperwise Ventures, and SentinelOne’s S Ventures. N47 is a global venture capital firm …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequence Raises $20 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/sequence-raises-20-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sequence, a London- and New York-based startup building AI-driven solutions to automate revenue operations, has raised $20 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by 645 Ventures, with participation from a16z, Firstminute Capital, Vor Capital, Passion Capital, and Dig Ventures. Notably, several high-profile founders and executives, including …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Verisoul Raises $8.8 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/verisoul-raises-8-8-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Verisoul, an Austin, Texas–based all-in-one platform for stopping fake accounts and fraud, has raised $8.8 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by High Alpha, with participation from Lookout Ventures, Bain Future Back Ventures, Bitkraft, and Third Prime. Based in Indianapolis, High Alpha is a venture studio …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recho Raises ¥300 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/recho-raises-300-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recho, a Tokyo, Japan-based provider of an AI-native voice AI platform, has raised ¥300 million ($2.2M) in a Series A round. Investors The round was led by SBI Investment Co., Ltd., a venture capital firm based in Tokyo, Japan. The firm offers investment management, investment consulting, and other services, serving …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:57 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Runware Raises $50 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/runware-raises-50-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Runware, a San Francisco, CA–based technology company that provides a unified API for generative AI developers, has raised $50 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Dawn Capital, with participation from Comcast Ventures, Speedinvest, Insight Partners, and a16z Speedrun. Dawn Capital is a European specialist B2B …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[InsightX Raises ¥600 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/insightx-raises-600-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[InsightX, a Tokyo, Japan–based provider of an AI platform for personalized customer experiences, has raised ¥600 million in the first close of its Series A round. Investors The round was led through a third-party allotment to DNX Ventures, a globally focused venture capital firm specializing in early-stage B2B startups. Founded …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Double Raises $6.5 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/double-raises-6-5-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Double, a New York-based AI-driven close management and practice management platform for accounting and bookkeeping firms, has raised $6.5 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Album Ventures, with participation from returning investor Jack Altman, Y Combinator, and earlier investors Mathilde Collin, Rahul Vohra, and William …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trendtracker Raises $7 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/trendtracker-raises-7-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trendtracker, a Ghent, Belgium-based AI-powered strategic intelligence platform for global organizations, has raised $7 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Armilar, with participation from existing investor Capricorn Partners. Armilar Venture Partners is an early-stage venture capital (VC) firm focused on investing in disruptive technology teams, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equixly Raises €10 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/equixly-raises-10-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Equixly, a Verona, Italy-based cybersecurity company that provides an AI-driven platform for automated API security testing, has raised €10 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by 33N Ventures, with participation from Alpha Intelligence Capital and existing investors JME Ventures, 360 Capital, and Fondazione Cassa di Risparmio …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bobyard Raises $35 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/bobyard-raises-35-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bobyard, a San Francisco, CA–based AI-driven construction technology company, has raised $35 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by 8VC, with participation from Pear VC, Primary Venture Partners, Tishman Speyer, RXR, Caffeinated Capital, and Merrick Ventures. 8VC is a venture capital firm founded in 2015 and …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nevis Secures $35 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/nevis-secures-35-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nevis, a New York-based AI platform for wealth management, has secured $35 million in a Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Sequoia Capital, with participation from ICONIQ and Ribbit Capital. Sequoia Capital is a venture capital firm headquartered in Menlo Park, California. The firm specializes in …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:58 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CoreOps.AI Raises $3.5M Pre-Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/coreops-ai-raises-3-5m-pre-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CoreOps.AI, a Noida, India-based enterprise software startup, has raised $3.5 million in a pre-Series A round. Investors The round was led by Siana Capital Management, with participation from Kettlebrough, Aroa Venture Partners, and several individual investors. Siana Capital Management is an India-based venture capital (VC) firm founded in 2017, focused …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scowtt Raises $12 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/scowtt-raises-12-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Scowtt, a Seattle, WA-based AI advertising optimization startup, has raised $12 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Inspired Capital, with participation from LiveRamp Ventures, Angeles Investors, and Angeles Ventures. Inspired Capital is a New York–based venture capital firm founded in 2019. The firm primarily invests …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aaru Secures Series A Funding]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/aaru-secures-series-a-funding</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aaru, a San Francisco, CA-based AI synthetic research startup, has secured a Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Redpoint Ventures, with previous seed and pre-seed investors including A*, Abstract Ventures, General Catalyst, Accenture Ventures, and Z Fellows. Redpoint Ventures is a venture capital firm founded in …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rail-Flow Raises €12.5 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/rail-flow-raises-12-5-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rail-Flow, a Frankfurt, Germany–based B2B transport-management platform for rail freight and intermodal logistics, has raised €12.5 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Trill Impact and Bonsai Partners, with participation from Climentum Capital, several business angels, and existing investors Rethink Ventures and Futury Capital. Founded in …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LUC Raises ¥120 Million Pre-Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/luc-raises-120-million-pre-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[LUC, a Tokyo, Japan-based provider of an AI and experience analysis platform, has raised ¥120 million in a pre-Series A round. Investors The round was led by NOW Inc. and Mizuho Capital Co., Ltd., bringing LUC’s total funding, including the seed round, to ¥150 million. NOW Inc. is a Tokyo-based …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vambe Raises $14 Million in Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/vambe-raises-14-million-in-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vambe, a Santiago, Chile-based AI-powered conversational commerce platform for B2C businesses, has raised $14 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Monashees, with participation from Cathay Latam, Atlantico, Tekton Ventures, and existing investors including Chile Ventures, SkyDeck Berkeley, Nazca, and M13. Monashees is a Brazilian venture …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pack Secures €5.8 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/pack-secures-5-8-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pack, a Bologna, Italy-based AI-native HR tech startup, has raised €5.8 million in a Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Rialto VC (initial tranche) and included US-based Acadian Ventures (second trance), along with HR and SaaS industry figures such as David Clarke, Thomas Otter, Jason Corsello, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LendOS Completes Series A Round]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/lendos-completes-series-a-round</link>
            <description><![CDATA[LendOS, a Miami, Florida–based fintech platform purpose-built for private credit lifecycle operations, has completed its Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Blackstone Innovations Investments, with participation from Illuminate Financial and Liberty City Ventures. Blackstone Innovations Investments is the strategic, early-stage investment arm of Blackstone’s Technology and Innovations …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sionic AI Raises ₩25 Billion Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/sionic-ai-raises-25-billion-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sionic AI, a Seoul, South Korea–based enterprise AI solutions company, has raised ₩25 billion ($18.1M) in Series A funding. Investors The funding round was led by Atinum Investment and LB Investment, with participation from strategic and financial investors including Naver Cloud, IBK Industrial Bank of Korea, IMM Investment, KT Investment, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rencore Extends Series A Funding to $15 Million]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/rencore-extends-series-a-funding-to-15-million</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rencore, a Munich, Germany-based software company that provides a cloud-based governance platform, has extended its Series A funding to $15 million. Investors The round was led by Hi Inov, with continued participation from UVC Partners and Capnamic Ventures. Hi Inov is a European B2B venture capital fund founded by entrepreneurs …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automat Raises $15.5 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/automat-raises-15-5-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Automat, a San Francisco, California–based company that specializes in AI-driven automation solutions, has raised $15.5 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Felicis, with participation from Initialized Capital, Khosla Ventures, Y Combinator, K5 Global, and Input Capital, bringing Automat's total funding to $19.25 million. Felicis is …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Onlayer Raises $8.2 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/onlayer-raises-8-2-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Onlayer, an Ankara, Türkiye-based regtech and end-to-end merchant management platform, has raised $8.2 million in a Series A funding round. Investors The round was led by Oleka Capital, with participation from multiple regional and international investors. Oleka Capital is a venture capital and growth equity firm based in Istanbul, Türkiye, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tidalwave Raises $22 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/tidalwave-raises-22-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tidalwave, a New York-based agentic AI-powered mortgage point-of-sale (POS) platform, has raised $22 million in Series A funding. Investors The round was led by Permanent Capital, with participation from D.R. Horton, Inc., and a follow-on from Engineering Capital. Permanent Capital is a Chicago-based expansion-stage venture capital firm that partners with …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augmentt Secures CAD $18 Million Series A]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thesaasnews.com/news/augmentt-secures-cad-18-million-series-a</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Augmentt, an Ottawa, Canada–based SaaS platform built for MSPs to unify and secure their clients' Microsoft 365 environments, has secured a CAD $18 million Series A financing round. Investors The round was led by Camber Partners, a New York City–based growth equity firm that partners with growth-stage B2B SaaS companies, …]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:01 -0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
